Berliner Gramophone Disc Collection
Yale University Music Library
- Recordings, Series I
  - Cui "La pomniu uecher" (I remember the evening), 1901; 1 (Box 732, Item barcode 39002125007501)
    Disc No. 22601
  - Romans Vrangel (In My Soul), undated; 1 (Box 732, Item barcode 39002125007519)
    Disc No. 22602
  - Barkarolla iz op.: "Fra Diavolo", 1901; 1 (Box 732, Item barcode 39002125007527)
    Disc No. 22605
  - N.N. Figner: Fra Diavolo; Barcarollo, undated; 1 (Box 732, Item barcode 39002125007535)
  - Ei Romano Morskogo, undated; 1 (Box 732, Item barcode 39002125007543)
    Disc No. 22617
  - Pikova Dama CR, 1901; 1 (Box 732, Item barcode 39002125007550)
    Disc No. 22618
  - Buchtojaroff, undated; 1 (Box 732, Item barcode 39002128474294)
    Disc No. 22620
  - Buchtojaroff, undated; 1 (Box 732, Item barcode 39002125007576)
    Disc No. 22621
  - Zastol 'naia Piesnia iz op. Traviata, undated; 1 (Box 732, Item barcode 39002125007584)
    Disc No. 22654
  - N.A. Rostovskii Thomas; Mignon; Wilhelm's Song, undated; 1 (Box 732, Item barcode 39002125007592)
    Disc No. 22702
  - Liubov; Romane; Vrangelia; R. Bernardi; Art. Imp. Moskovskoi Opery; Moskau, undated; 1 (Box 732, Item barcode 39002125007600)
    Disc No. 22785
  - Polish Tenor, undated; 1 (Box 732, Item barcode 39002125007618)
    Disc No. 22956
  - Russian Baritone, undated; 1 (Box 732, Item barcode 39002125007626)
    Disc No. 22974
  - F.D. Augustoff: Russian Baritone, undated; 1 (Box 732, Item barcode 39002125007634)
    Disc No. 22995
  - Russian Baritone, undated; 1 (Box 732, Item barcode 39002125007642)
    Disc No. 2-22002
  - Moriuszko, Holka, undated; 1 (Box 732, Item barcode 39002125007659)
    Disc No. 22063
  - P.I. Platonoff (V) Romance, undated; 1 (Box 732, Item barcode 39002125007667)
    Disc No. 2-22070
  - S.D. Lenskiy: Rigoletto: La donna e mobile, undated; 1 (Box 732, Item barcode 39002125007675)
    Disc No. 2-22075
  - M.A. Malis "Ne dlia menia pridet vesna" (The spring will come not for me), undated; 1 (Box 732, Item barcode 39002125007683)
    Disc No. 2-22084
  - Russian Tenor: Rubinstein, undated; 1 (Box 732, Item barcode 39002125667957)
    Disc No. 22277
  - Russian Tenor: Eugene Onegin, Lenskiy's Aria, undated; 1 (Box 732, Item barcode 39002125667965)
    Disc No. 22274
  - M.A. Max (KS) "Lastocka", undated; 1 (Box 733, Item barcode 39002125007709)
    Disc No. 2-22089
  - "Ty pomnish'-ni nvd morem my sidieli", undated; 1 (Box 733, Item barcode 39002125007717)
    Disc No. 2-22215
  - A.M. Labinskii, undated; 1 (Box 733, Item barcode 39002125007725)
    Disc No. 2-22233
  - Bleichman, "Pridesh li ty linbov" ("Will you come, love") A.M. Labinskii, undated; 1 (Box 733, Item barcode 39002125007733)
    Disc No. 2-22236
  - "S toboi mnie pobyt' khotielos'", undated; 1 (Box 733, Item barcode 39002125007741)
    Disc No. 2-22249
  - A.D. Davydoo dishin "Zabyty nieshnyia lobrania", undated; 1 (Box 733, Item barcode 39002125007758)
    Disc No. 2-22346
  - "Ne veliat' Meshie za nachen'kie khodit'" ("Masha shouldn't cross the river"), Russian song, M.M. Chuprynnikov, undated; 1 (Box 733, Item barcode 39002125007766)
    Disc No. 2-22353
  - Ty i Vy sl. Pushkina, undated; 1 (Box 733, Item barcode 39002125007774)
    Disc No. 2-22359
  - "Kak' mnie bol'no" romans, muz. Rakhmaninoua, undated; 1 (Box 733, Item barcode 39002125007782)
    Disc No. 2-22362
  - Aria Pauline, undated; 1 (Box 733, Item barcode 39002125007790)
    Disc No. 23063
  - A.D. Viaztseva, undated; 1 (Box 733, Item barcode 39002125007808)
    Disc No. 23073
  - Gramophone; R.M. Raisova, undated; 1 (Box 733, Item barcode 39002125007816)
    Disc No. 23074x
  - Solovey Aliab'eva; T.P. Gorchakova, undated; 1 (Box 733, Item barcode 39002125007824)
    Disc No. 23078
  - L.N. Bragina; Spring Song, undated; 1 (Box 733, Item barcode 39002125007832)
    Disc No. 23204
  - R.M. Raisova; Gypsy song: "Ta ne igraiu vorse Vami" ("I don't play with you at all"), undated; 1 (Box 733, Item barcode 39002125007840)
    Disc No. 23251
  - "Ta vas zhdala" Gypsy song; R.M. Raisova, undated; 1 (Box 733, Item barcode 39002125007857)
    Disc No. 23252
  - A.A. Guozdetskaia, undated; 1 (Box 733, Item barcode 39002125007865)
    Disc No. 23270
  - Gvodjetzkaja, undated; 1 (Box 733, Item barcode 39002125007873)
    Disc No. 23274
  - Russian Soprano, undated; 1 (Box 733, Item barcode 39002125007881)
    Disc No. 23527
  - "Ostav' ego" ("Leave Him"), undated; 1 (Box 733, Item barcode 39002125007899)
    Disc No. 23528
  - Estonian Soprano, undated; 1 (Box 733, Item barcode 39002125007907)
    Disc No. 23556
  - Oieke (Hildach), undated; 1 (Box 733, Item barcode 39002125007915)
    Disc No. 23558
  - Varia Panina, undated; 1 (Box 733, Item barcode 39002125007923)
    Disc No. 23588
  - Varia Panina, undated; 1 (Box 733, Item barcode 39002125007931)
    Disc No. 23589
  - Russian Contralto, undated; 1 (Box 733, Item barcode 39002125007949)
    Disc No. 23591
  - "Otoydi" Romans Davydova, undated; 1 (Box 733, Item barcode 39002125007956)
    Disc No. 23595
  - Ia ne skazhutebie rom. O. De-Bore, undated; 1 (Box 733, Item barcode 39002125007964)
    Disc No. 23601
  - Vy menia plienili Tsyganskiv Romanc, undated; 1 (Box 733, Item barcode 39002125007972)
    Disc No. 23602
  - Zastol'naia piesn' iz. op. "Traviata" muz. Verdi, undated; 1 (Box 733, Item barcode 39002125007980)
    Disc No. 23626
  - Labinskii and Andreev, undated; 1 (Box 733, Item barcode 39002125007998)
    Disc No. 24016
  - Mr. and Mrs. Romanchenko, undated; 1 (Box 733, Item barcode 39002125008004)
    Disc No. 24018
  - A.M. Labinsii and V.S. Sharonoff, undated; 1 (Box 733, Item barcode 39002125008012)
    Disc No. 24037
  - M. Mikhailova and L. Bragina, undated; 1 (Box 733, Item barcode 39002125008020)
    Disc No. 24150
  - M. Mikhailowa and L. Bragina, undated; 1 (Box 733, Item barcode 39002125008038)
    Disc No. 24151
  - F.D. Augustoff (v) and L.M. Derzhavin, undated; 1 (Box 733, Item barcode 39002125008046)
    Disc No. 24195
  - Russian Duet, undated; 1 (Box 733, Item barcode 39002125008053)
    Disc No. 24223
  - Dargomyzhskii, "Van'ka-Tan'ka", undated; 1 (Box 733, Item barcode 39002125008061)
    Disc No. 2-24307
  - French Talking: La Famille Legros dit par Monsieur Gabin de la Cigale, undated; 1 (Box 733, Item barcode 39002125008079)
    Disc No. 31012
  - French Bass: Priere (Ch. Gounod), undated; 1 (Box 733, Item barcode 39002125008087)
    Disc No. 32012
  - Laffitte, undated; 1 (Box 733, Item barcode 39002125008095)
    Disc No. 32038
  - Salut! O Mon Dernier Matin, undated; 1 (Box 733, Item barcode 39002125008103)
    Disc No. 32305
  - Faust: Scene De L'Eglise (Gounod). Sung by René Fournets., undated; 1 (Box 733, Item barcode 39002125008111)
    Disc No. 32466
  - Thomas Salignae, undated; 1 (Box 733, Item barcode 39002125008129)
    Disc No. 32306
  - French Bass: Hamlet; Comme une pale fleur chante Monsieur Aumonier, undated; 1 (Box 733, Item barcode 39002125008137)
    Disc No. 32438
  - Aumonier, undated; 1 (Box 733, Item barcode 39002125008145)
    Disc No. 32445
  - French Bass: Robert Le Diable (Meyerbeer): Valse Infernale chante par Mr. Aumonier, undated; 1 (Box 733, Item barcode 39002125008152)
    Disc No. 32446
  - Fournets, undated; 1 (Box 733, Item barcode 39002125008160)
    Disc No. 32471
  - French Bass: La Chalet Vallons de L'Helvetie Chante par M. Fournets, undated; 1 (Box 733, Item barcode 39002125008178)
    Disc No. 32474
  - Fournets, undated; 1 (Box 733, Item barcode 39002125008186)
    Disc No. 32480
  - Rub. BV-72 qv., undated; 1 (Box 733, Item barcode 39002125008194)
    Disc No. 32576
  - Le Grand Mogol Chante Par Monsieur B.R. Paris, undated; 1 (Box 733, Item barcode 39002125008202)
    Disc No. 32590
  - Berceuse Jocelyn Chante par Monsieur Chapini Paris, undated; 1 (Box 733, Item barcode 39002125008210)
    Disc No. 32632
  - Roberile Diable, undated; 1; This disc is damaged. A small section on the outer edge of the disc has chipped off. The broken section has been retained and is housed with the original disc. (Box 733, Item barcode 39002125008228)
    Disc No. 32635
  - Tambour Masor Air du Caid, undated; 1 (Box 733, Item barcode 39002125008236)
    Disc No. 32639
  - Scene Del'Eglise Faust, undated; 1 (Box 734, Item barcode 39002125667734)
    Disc No. 32643
  - "Divine Volupte", undated; 1 (Box 734, Item barcode 39002125008285)
    Disc No. 32645
  - Scene de L'Eglise Faust, undated; 1 (Box 734, Item barcode 39002125008293)
    Disc No. 32646
  - Stances de Lakme chante par monsieur sacreau, undated; 1 (Box 734, Item barcode 39002125008301)
    Disc No. 32648
  - Chanson du Todeador Carmen, undated; 1 (Box 734, Item barcode 39002125008319)
    Disc No. 32649
  - Soulacroix (Basoche), undated; 1 (Box 734, Item barcode 39002125008327)
    Disc No. 32656
  - Le Veau D'ar Chante Par Monsieur R. Fournets, undated; 1 (Box 734, Item barcode 39002125008335)
    Disc No. 32664
  - French Bass: Faust Le Veau D'or, undated; 1 (Box 734, Item barcode 39002125008343)
  - Serenade de Faust Chante Par Monsieur R. Fournets de L'Opera, undated; 1 (Box 734, Item barcode 39002125008350)
    Disc No. 32665
  - French Bass: Faust Serenade, undated; 1 (Box 734, Item barcode 39002125008368)
    Disc No. 32665x
  - French Baritone, undated; 1 (Box 734, Item barcode 39002125008376)
    Disc No. 32673
  - French Baritone: Le Pardon de Ploermel, undated; 1 (Box 734, Item barcode 39002125008384)
    Disc No. 32674
  - French Baritone: Serenade de Don Juan (Mozart), undated; 1 (Box 734, Item barcode 39002125008392)
    Disc No. 32675
  - Fournets, undated; 1 (Box 734, Item barcode 39002125008400)
    Disc No. 32689
  - Rossini, undated; 1 (Box 734, Item barcode 39002125008418)
    Disc No. 32691
  - French Tenor; Girand Martha, undated; 1 (Box 734, Item barcode 39002125008426)
    Disc No. 32692
  - [indecipherable], undated; 1 (Box 734, Item barcode 39002125008434)
    Disc No. 32699
  - French Tenor: Carmen-Bizet, undated; 1 (Box 734, Item barcode 39002125008442)
    Disc No. 32720
  - [indecipherable], undated; 1 (Box 734, Item barcode 39002125008459)
    Disc No. 32721
  - Le Reve, undated; 1 (Box 734, Item barcode 39002125008467)
    Disc No. 32854
  - Soulacroix, undated; 1 (Box 734, Item barcode 39002125008475)
    Disc No. 32855
  - Soulacroix, undated; 1 (Box 734, Item barcode 39002125008483)
    Disc No. 32879
  - French Baritone: Couplets des enfants, undated; 1 (Box 734, Item barcode 39002125008491)
    Disc No. 32881
  - French Baritone: Spectre infernal, undated; 1 (Box 734, Item barcode 39002125008509)
    Disc No. 32882
  - French Cohique, undated; 1 (Box 734, Item barcode 39002125008517)
    Disc No. 32893
  - French, La Mascotte, undated; 1 (Box 734, Item barcode 39002125009887)
    Disc No. 32911
  - French Bass Baritone: Les Rameaux, undated; 1 (Box 734, Item barcode 39002125008533)
    Disc No. 32973
  - French Bass: La Chanson de Marinette, undated; 1 (Box 734, Item barcode 39002125008541)
    Disc No. 32979x
  - French Tenor: La Juive (Halevy) Rachel quand du Seigneur chante par Monsieur Cheyrat Paris, undated; 1 (Box 734, Item barcode 39002125008558)
    Disc No. 32984
  - French Tenor: Sigurd (Rayer): J'ai Garde mon ame ingenue chante par Monsieur Laffitte de l'Opera, undated; 1 (Box 734, Item barcode 39002125008566)
    Disc No. 32987
  - French Tenor: Sigurd (Rayer) Prince du Rhin chante par Monsieur Laffitte de l'Opera, undated; 1 (Box 734, Item barcode 39002125008574)
    Disc No. 32988
  - Laffitte, undated; 1 (Box 734, Item barcode 39002125008582)
    Disc No. 32989
  - French Bass: Robert Le Diable (Meyerbeer) Evocation chante par Monsieur Aumonier, undated; 1 (Box 734, Item barcode 39002125008590)
    Disc No. 32995
  - French Baritone: Le Jour et La Nuit, undated; 1 (Box 734, Item barcode 39002125008608)
    Disc No. 2-32002
  - French Baritone: Les Louis D'Or (Pierre Dupont), undated; 1 (Box 734, Item barcode 39002125008616)
    Disc No. 2-32038
  - French Baritone: Charite (Faure), undated; 1 (Box 734, Item barcode 39002125008624)
    Disc No. 2-32063
  - French Bass: Les Huguenots (Meyerbeer), undated; 1 (Box 734, Item barcode 39002125008632)
    Disc No. 2-32080
  - French Soprano: L'air de Michaela, 1900 July 8; 1 (Box 734, Item barcode 39002125008640)
    Disc No. 33166
  - French Sobrano, undated; 1 (Box 734, Item barcode 39002125008657)
    Disc No. 33169
  - French Sobrano, undated; 1 (Box 734, Item barcode 39002125008665)
    Disc No. 33172
  - Habanera- Carmen Bizet, undated; 1 (Box 734, Item barcode 39002125008673)
    Disc No. 33174
  - Chanson du Capitaine, undated; 1 (Box 734, Item barcode 39002125008681)
    Disc No. 33179
  - French Sobrano, undated; 1 (Box 734, Item barcode 39002125008699)
    Disc No. 33181
  - Le Pardon De Pidermel (Meyerbeer), undated; 1 (Box 734, Item barcode 39002125009895)
    Disc No. 33193
  - La Perle du Bresil, undated; 1 (Box 734, Item barcode 39002125008707)
    Disc No. 33196
  - French Sobrano, undated; 1 (Box 734, Item barcode 39002125008715)
    Disc No. 33212
  - French Sobrano, undated; 1 (Box 734, Item barcode 39002125008723)
    Disc No. 33216
  - Diartoy in B, undated; 1 (Box 734, Item barcode 39002125008731)
    Disc No. 33217
  - Guillon-Brasseur, undated; 1 (Box 734, Item barcode 39002125008749)
    Disc No. 33224
  - Valse de Romeo et Juliette, undated; 1 (Box 734, Item barcode 39002125008756)
    Disc No. 33219
  - French Mez Soprano: Mignon (Thomas) Connais tu le pays chante par Madame Guillon-Brasseur, undated; 1 (Box 734, Item barcode 39002125008764)
    Disc No. 33225
  - French Mez Soprano: Mignon (Thomas) Connais tu le pays chante par Madame Guillon-Brassuer Paris, undated; 1 (Box 734, Item barcode 39002125008772)
    Disc No. 33225x
  - French Mez Soprano: Le Prophete (Meyerbeer) Couplets de la mendiante Donnez donnez chante par Madame Guillon Brasseur, undated; 1 (Box 734, Item barcode 39002125008780)
    Disc No. 33227
  - French Mez Soprano: L'Africaine (Meyerbeer) Air de Slika: Sur mes genoux chante par Madame Guillon-Brasseur, undated; 1 (Box 734, Item barcode 39002125008798)
    Disc No. 33229
  - French Mez Soprano: La Boudeuse chante par Madame Guillon Brasseur, undated; 1 (Box 734, Item barcode 39002125008806)
    Disc No. 33243
  - French Mez Soprano: Pourquoi Je T'aime chante par Madame Guillon-Brasseur, undated; 1 (Box 734, Item barcode 39002125008814)
    Disc No. 33247
  - Le Concert Dans Le Feuillage joue par Monsieur Demont, undated; 1 (Box 735, Item barcode 39002126520791)
    Disc No. 39169
  - Monolog a Hamlet III Act. gesprochen von Mathieu Lutzenkirchen, undated; 1 (Box 735, Item barcode 39002126520809)
    Disc No. 41050X
  - Drei Lozelach (Witze) gesprochen von Heinr. Eisenbach Wien., undated; 1 (Box 735, Item barcode 39002126520817)
    Disc No. 41086
  - Beim Zahnarzt gesprochen von Martin Bendix, undated; 1 (Box 735, Item barcode 39002126520825)
    Disc No. 41099x
  - Das Gascognerlied aus Cyrano von Bergerac gesprochen von Josef Kainz, undated; 1 (Box 735, Item barcode 39002126520833)
    Disc No. 41222
  - [indecipherable], undated; 1 (Box 735, Item barcode 39002126520841)
    Disc No. 42012
  - [indecipherable], undated; 1 (Box 735, Item barcode 39002126520858)
    Disc No. 42015
  - [indecipherable], undated; 1 (Box 735, Item barcode 39002126520866)
    Disc No. 42018
  - Standchen a Faust, undated; 1 (Box 735, Item barcode 39002126520874)
    Disc No. 42019
  - Winkelmann, undated; 1 (Box 735, Item barcode 39002126520882)
    Disc No. 42016
  - O Strassburg du wunderschone Stadt gesungen von Robert Leonhardt, undated; 1 (Box 735, Item barcode 39002126520890)
    Disc No. 42025
  - German Tenor [indecipherable], undated; 1 (Box 735, Item barcode 39002126520908)
    Disc No. 42026
  - German Baritone: Gaudeamus igitur gesungen von Robert Leonhardt, undated; 1 (Box 735, Item barcode 39002126520916)
    Disc No. 42037
  - German Tenor: Lass dir Zeit, undated; 1 (Box 735, Item barcode 39002126520924)
    Disc No. 42043
  - German Tenor: Standchen aus Troubadour gensungen von Fritz Chrooter k.u.k. Kammersanger, undated; 1 (Box 735, Item barcode 39002126520932)
    Disc No. 42071
  - German Tenor: Siciliana a. Cavalleria Rusticana gesungen von K.K. Hofopernsanger Leo Slezak, undated; 1 (Box 735, Item barcode 39002126520940)
    Disc No. 42081
  - German Tenor: Siciliana a. Cavalleria Rusticana gesungen von K.K. Hofopernisanger Leo Slezak, undated; 1 (Box 735, Item barcode 39002126520957)
    Disc No. 42081-II
  - German Tenor: Liebeslied a. Tannhauser gesungen von K.K. Hofopernsanger Leo Slezak Wien, undated; 1 (Box 735, Item barcode 39002126520965)
    Disc No. 42082
  - German Tenor: Liebeslied a. Tannhauser gesungen von K.K. Hofopernsanger Leo Slezak Wien, undated; 1 (Box 735, Item barcode 39002126520973)
    Disc No. 2nd Stake
  - German Tenor: Liebeslied aus Tannhauser gesungen von K.K. Hofopernsanger Leo Slezak Wien, undated; 1 (Box 735, Item barcode 39002126520981)
  - Ungeduld v.Franz Schubert gesungen von K.K. Hofopernsanger Leo Slezak, undated; 1 (Box 735, Item barcode 39002126520999)
    Disc No. 42083
  - German Baritone: Das Staarl von Karl Kapeller gesungen von Rudolf Seibold Wien, undated; 1 (Box 735, Item barcode 39002126521005)
    Disc No. 42085 II
  - Auf Flugeln des Gesanges, undated; 1 (Box 735, Item barcode 39002126521013)
    Disc No. 42164
  - Auf Flugeln des Gesanges, undated; 1 (Box 735, Item barcode 39002126521021)
  - German Tenor: O wie so trugerisch a. Rigoletto gesungen von Marian Alma, undated; 1 (Box 735, Item barcode 39002126521039)
    Disc No. 42183
  - German Baritone: An der Weser gesungen von Gustav Waschow, undated; 1 (Box 735, Item barcode 39002126521047)
    Disc No. 42188
  - German Tenor: Standchen aus Troubadour v. Verdi gesungen von Marian Alma, undated; 1 (Box 735, Item barcode 39002126521054)
    Disc No. 42208
  - German Baritone: Zsipan's Entreelied a. Zigeunerbaron gesungen von Oscar Wallner Munchen, undated; 1 (Box 735, Item barcode 39002126521062)
    Disc No. 42265
  - Im tiefen Keller gesungen von Georg Sieglitz Munchen, undated; 1 (Box 735, Item barcode 39002126521070)
    Disc No. 42290
  - German Baritone: Fliedermonolog a.Meistersinger I gesungen von Dr. Rudolf Proll Frankfurt a.M, undated; 1 (Box 735, Item barcode 39002126521088)
    Disc No. 42292
  - German Tenor: Standchen aus Troubadour gesungen von Siegmund Krauss Wiesbaden, undated; 1 (Box 735, Item barcode 39002126521096)
    Disc No. 42295
  - German Tenor: Man wird ja einmal nurgeboren a.Waffenschmied gesungen von Hermann Schramm Frankfurt a.M., undated; 1 (Box 735, Item barcode 39002126521104)
    Disc No. 42301
  - Abschied vom Liebchen von Ehrke gesungen von Felix Muller Berlin, undated; 1 (Box 735, Item barcode 39002126521112)
    Disc No. 42521
  - German Bass: In diesen heiligen Hallengesungen von Paul Knupfer, undated; 1 (Box 735, Item barcode 39002126521120)
    Disc No. 42194
  - German Tenor: Vaier Mutter a. Undine gesungen von Herm. Schramm Frankfurt a.M., undated; 1 (Box 735, Item barcode 39002126521138)
    Disc No. 42294
  - German Tenor: Nord-Express a Schoen war's doch gesungen von Joseph Josephi, undated; 1 (Box 735, Item barcode 39002126521146)
    Disc No. 42470
  - German Tenor: Schwanenlied Lohengrin gesungen von Marian Alma Berlin, undated; 1 (Box 735, Item barcode 39002126521153)
    Disc No. 42536
  - [indecipherable], 1899; 1 (Box 735, Item barcode 39002126521161)
    Disc No. 42597
  - Gesungen von Robert Leonhardt Berlin, undated; 1 (Box 735, Item barcode 39002126521179)
    Disc No. 42621
  - German Tenor: Lache Bajazzo gesungen von Paul Weiss, undated; 1 (Box 735, Item barcode 39002126521187)
    Disc No. 42666
  - German Tenor: La Paloma (Die Taube) gesungen von Marian Alma Kgl. Hofopernsanger, undated; 1 (Box 735, Item barcode 39002126521195)
    Disc No. 42673
  - German Baritone with Orchestra Gern gab'ich Glanz und Reichthum hm aus Waffenschmied gesungen von Gustav Waschow, undated; 1 (Box 735, Item barcode 39002126521203)
    Disc No. 42674
  - German Baritone with Orchestra: Trinklied Des Kaspar, undated; 1 (Box 735, Item barcode 39002126521211)
    Disc No. 42687
  - German Tenor: Das Muhlrad Volkslied gesungen von K.U.K. Kammersanger Franz Naval Wien, undated; 1 (Box 735, Item barcode 39002126521229)
    Disc No. 42702
  - German Tenor: Verschwiegene Liebe, undated; 1 (Box 735, Item barcode 39002126521237)
    Disc No. 42703
  - German Tenor: Selig sind, die verfolgung leiden gesungen von K.U.K. Kammersanger Erik Schmedes Wien, undated; 1 (Box 735, Item barcode 39002126521245)
    Disc No. 42708
  - German Tenor: Mir traumte einst ein schoner Traum, undated; 1 (Box 735, Item barcode 39002126521252)
    Disc No. 42709
  - German Tenor: Verwelkt, von V. Boschetti, undated; 1 (Box 735, Item barcode 39002126521260)
    Disc No. 42738
  - German Bass: Wenn ich einmal der Herrgott war, undated; 1 (Box 735, Item barcode 39002126521278)
    Disc No. 42752
  - German Tenor: Pastorale aus Prophet, undated; 1 (Box 735, Item barcode 39002126521286)
    Disc No. 42755
  - [indecipherable], undated; 1 (Box 735, Item barcode 39002126521294)
    Disc No. 42756
  - [indecipherable], undated; 1 (Box 735, Item barcode 39002126521302)
    Disc No. 42757
  - German Tenor: Loblied der Venus, undated; 1 (Box 735, Item barcode 39002126521310)
    Disc No. 42758
  - German Tenor: Siciliana a. Cavalleria Rusticana, undated; 1 (Box 735, Item barcode 39002126521328)
    Disc No. 42763
  - Wiegenlied von Brahms; K.U.K. Hafopernsangerin Frances Saville, undated; 1 (Box 736, Item barcode 39002125008822)
    Disc No. 43184
  - Auf Flugeln aes Gesanges; Irene Abendroth; Kgl. Sachs. Hofopernsangerin, undated; 1 (Box 736, Item barcode 39002125008830)
    Disc No. 43181
  - Zigennerlid aus Zigeunerbaron; Philla Siegmann-Wolff, undated; 1 (Box 736, Item barcode 39002125008848)
    Disc No. 43178
  - Draussen am Wall von Sevilla; Marie Gutheil-Schoder (Hofoper), undated; 1 (Box 736, Item barcode 39002125008855)
    Disc No. 43175
  - Orlofsky-Lied; Josephine Braus, undated; 1 (Box 736, Item barcode 39002125008863)
    Disc No. 43169
  - Jolonaise Qulliginon; Freud Baumann, undated; 1 (Box 736, Item barcode 39002125008871)
    Disc No. 43137
  - [unintelligible]; Freud Baumann, undated; 1 (Box 736, Item barcode 39002125008889)
    Disc No. 43135
  - Goldfischlied a Geisha; Philla Siegmann-Wolf, undated; 1 (Box 736, Item barcode 39002125008897)
    Disc No. H3121
  - Draussen am Wall von Sevilla a Carmen; Fraulein Destinn, Kgl. Hofopernsangerin, undated; 1 (Box 736, Item barcode 39002125008905)
    Disc No. 43116
  - Ein Kleines Lied with Meyer Stolzenau; Frau Engelen - Sewing, undated; 1 (Box 736, Item barcode 39002125008913)
    Disc No. 43104
  - Es blinktder Thau v. Rubinstein; Elsa Schweizer; 43093, undated; 1 (Box 736, Item barcode 39002125008921)
    Disc No. 43098
  - Polonaise a Mignon; Hedi Kaufmann; 43094, undated; 1 (Box 736, Item barcode 39002125008939)
    Disc No. 43094
  - Arie a. Barbier von Sevilla II; Hedi Kaufmann; 43093, undated; 1 (Box 736, Item barcode 39002125008947)
    Disc No. 43093
  - Gnaden-Arie a. Robert de Teufel; Hedi Kaufmann; 43091, undated; 1 (Box 736, Item barcode 39002125008954)
    Disc No. 43091
  - Gelb rollt mir zu Fussen v. Rubinstein; Martha Leffler-Burckhard; 43088, undated; 1 (Box 736, Item barcode 39002125008962)
    Disc No. 43088
  - Walkurenruf der Brunhilde a Walkure; Pelagie Greef-Andriesen; 43084, undated; 1 (Box 736, Item barcode 39002125008970)
    Disc No. 43084
  - Ballade a Derfliegende Hollander; Pelagie Greef-Andriesen; 43032, undated; 1 (Box 736, Item barcode 39002125008988)
    Disc No. 43082
  - Soldatenbraut v. Schumann; Kath Senger-Bettaque; 43072, undated; 1 (Box 736, Item barcode 39002125008996)
    Disc No. 43072
  - Madchen's Wunsch v. Chopin; Kath Senger-Bettaque; 43071, undated; 1 (Box 736, Item barcode 39002125009002)